Guide to the Chauncey M. Depew papers, 1856-1934 MS2095
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Speeches and articles, 1877-1927; MS2095 Series 2; 7 Linear feet (Box 10, Box 11, Box 8, Box 9, Box 6, Box 7, Box 4, Box 5, Box 16, Box 3, Box 15, Box 14, Box 13, Box 12)
  - Pamphlet, "Oration at the Celebration of the Birthday of Washington," Union League Club, Chicago, 02/22/1888 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Pamphlet, "Speech at the Congress of the Railway Employees of the Middle and Western States," Chicago, 02/24/1899 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Pamphlet, "The Government of the Philippine Islands," US Senate, 02/27/1900 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Pamphlet, "The Whole Question of Taxation and The Charter of Puerto Rican Self-Government," US Senate, 04/02/1900 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Pamphlet, "Trade Relations with Cuba," US Senate, 12/12/1903 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Pamphlet, "The Panama Canal," US Senate, 01/14/1904 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Pamphlet, "Memorial Address on the Late Senator Hanna," US Senate, 04/07/1904 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Pamphlet, "Oration at the Celebration of the Fortieth Anniversary of the Union League House," Philadelphia, 05/11/1905 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Pamphlet, "Forest Reserves and Alaska-Yukon-Pacific Exposition," US Senate, 02/22/1907-02/23/1907 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Pamphlet, "Reform of the Currency," US Senate, 02/25/1907 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Pamphlet, "In Memoriam, Remarks on the Life and Character of Hon. John H. Ketcham and Hon. William H. Flack," US Senate, 03/02/1907 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Pamphlet, "Fifteenth Celebration of the Birthday of CMD by the Montauk Club," Brooklyn, 04/27/1907 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Pamphlet, "American Mercantile Marine," US Senate, 02/24/1908 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Pamphlet, "The Currency Question and Alaska-Yukon-Pacific Exposition," US Senate, 02/1908 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Pamphlet, "Amendment of the National Banking Laws," US Senate, 03/06/1908 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Pamphlet, "Speech at the Taft and Hughes Meeting," Brooklyn, 10/26/1908 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Pamphlet, "Speech at the Dinner to the Republican Leader and Workers of the 27th Assembly District,", 11/14/1908 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Pamphlet, "Postal Savings Banks," US Senate, 12/15/1908 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Pamphlet, "Increase of salaries of the President, Vice-President, Speaker of the House of Representatives and Federal Judges," US Senate, 01/18/1909 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Pamphlet, "Memorial Exercises in Honor of the Late Senator William B. Allison," US Senate, 02/06/1909 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Pamphlet, "Civil Service Examinations in Census Appointments," US Senate, 04/10/1909 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Pamphlet, "Eighteenth Annual Dinner Celebration of the Birthday of CMD" by the Montauk Club, 04/26/1909 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Pamphlet, "The Tariff," US Senate, 05/17/1909 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Pamphlet, "The Finance Committee of the Senate and the People," US Senate, 06/15/1909 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Pamphlet, "Porto Rico - the Effort of the House of Delegates to Revolutionize the Government and Coerce the Congress...," US Senate, 07/09/1909 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Pamphlet, "The Resources of the Country and Its Prosperity Under Republican Policies," US Senate, 12/20/1909 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Pamphlet, "Birthday Speech of CMD," Senate Document No. 518, Journal of the US Senate, 61st Congress: 2nd Session, 05/02/1910 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Pamphlet, "Address at the 32nd Anniversary of the YMCA of New York," Association Hall, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Speeches and articles, undated (Box 7)
  - Birthday Addresses at the Montauk Club, 1892-1899 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Addresses - Lincoln's Birthday, University of Chicago, Birthday Dinner at the Montauk Club, 1895 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Speeches - Vermont SAR, NYU Hall of Fame, Lotos Club, Pan-American Exposition Railroad Day, Interview after Assassination of McKinley, South Carolina Inter-State and West-Indian Exposition, others, 1896-1902 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Speeches at the Republican Club - Upon Becoming President of the Club, on Lincoln's Birthday Commemoration, 1898 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Speeches - Before the College Women's Club, Independent Club, Order of Red Men, Norwich University, Gridiron Club, Republican Club, others, 1898-1900 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Speeches - Pilgrim Society, Lotos Club, Hungry Club, Automobile Club, 1907-1908 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Speeches - Japanese Society, Yale Alumni Association, Amen Corner, 16th Annual Birthday Dinner, 1908 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Speeches and articles, undated (Box 8)
  - Compiled Speeches, Orations and After Dinner Speeches, 1890 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Compiled Speeches, Life and Later Speeches - Limited Edition 98/100, 1894 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Compiled Speeches, Life and Later Speeches, 1894 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Speeches and articles, undated (Box 9)
  - Compiled Speeches, Life and Later Speeches, 1894 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Compiled Speeches, Life and Later Speeches, 1894 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Compiled Speeches, Orations and After Dinner Speeches, 1896 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Speeches and articles, undated (Box 10)
  - Compiled Speeches, Orations and After Dinner Speeches, 1896 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Compiled Speeches, Orations and After Dinner Speeches, 1896 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Compiled Speeches, Orations and After Dinner Speeches, 1896 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Speeches and articles, undated (Box 11)
  - Compiled Speeches, Orations and After Dinner Speeches, 1896 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Compiled Speeches, Orations, Speeches and Addresses, Volume I Orations and Memorial Addresses, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Compiled Speeches, Orations, Speeches and Addresses, Volume II Banquet and Dinner Speeches, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Speeches and articles, undated (Box 12)
  - Compiled Speeches, Orations, Speeches and Addresses, Volume III Anniversary and Birthday Addresses, 1910 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Compiled Speeches, Orations, Speeches and Addresses, Volume IV Club and Society Addresses, 1910 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Compiled Speeches, Orations, Speeches and Addresses, Volume V College and Educational Addresses, 1910 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Speeches and articles, undated (Box 13)
  - Compiled Speeches, Orations, Speeches and Addresses, Volume VI Political Speeches, 1910 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Compiled Speeches, Orations, Speeches and Addresses, Volume VII Speeches in the U.S. Senate, 1910 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Compiled Speeches, Orations, Speeches and Addresses, Volume VIII Miscellaneous Speeches, 1910 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Speeches and articles, undated (Box 14)
  - Compiled Speeches, Addresses and Literary Contributions on the Threshold of Eighty Two, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Compiled Speeches, Addresses and Literary Contributions on the Threshold of Eighty Two, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Compiled Speeches, Addresses and Literary Contributions on the Threshold of Eighty Two, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Speeches and articles, undated (Box 15)
  - Compiled Speeches, Addresses and Literary Contributions at Four-Score and Four, 1918 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Compiled Speeches, Addresses and Literary Contributions at Four-Score and Four, 1918 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Compiled Speeches, Addresses and Literary Contributions at Four-Score and Four, 1918 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Speeches and articles, undated (Box 16)
  - Speech fragment, "Latter part of speech on Sam Sloan," (Interview), 09/16/1891 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Speech fragment, p. 10, Balance of trade, after 1897, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Speech fragment, p. 2-4, Reminiscences after 77 years, 1912 ca. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Speech fragment, "The Civil War was between brothers...," p. 2, 1917-1918 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Speech fragment, Economics of war, p. 16 (possibly Christmas message), 1918 ca. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Speech fragment, Prosperity of US and foreign aid, p. 11, 1918-1919 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Speech fragment, Ninetieth Birthday, p. 7, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Speech fragment, Reminiscences - -Yale and early political life, p. 3-21, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Speech fragment, "The Senate is constantly represented as the billionaires club...," p. 10-16, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Speech fragment, "It added little to the happiness and liberty of mankind...," p. 3-11, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Speech fragment, "with nine thousand marched against Fort Duquesne...," (early US history), p. 10-17, (dedication of monument), undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Speech fragment, "years of adulation and attention..." p. 4, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Speech fragment, "Two illustrations of his power...," (Roosevelt), undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Speech fragment, Man and war, p. 9, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Speech fragment, "the affairs of the Confederacy...," p. 3, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Speech fragment, "the cartoonist and individualist...,", undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Speech fragment, "to define the elusive quality...," p. 33, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Speech fragments, various pages filed together, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Speech fragments, various pages filed together, undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Speech fragment, "the American people distrusted the man...," p. 4, (public speaking), undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Speech fragment, "an engagement to hear me at Syracuse...," p. 22-23, (re: Mr. Conkling's speech), undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Speech fragment, "We who are all right minded...," p. 2, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Speech fragment, "secures their happiness...," p. 16, undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Extracts from speeches and statements, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Notes for speech, after, 1912 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Notes for speech, "Luxurious rearing and a life of leisure...," (re: Roosevelt), undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Notes for speech, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Notes for speech, undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Notes for speech, (on card from The New York Farmers, 94th Dinner), undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Notes for speech, undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Notes for speech, (on envelope of The Waldorf Astoria), undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Notes for speech, (memorial to someone born 1844, died in office), undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Notes for speech, (dates of Vanderbilts and railroads), undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Notes for speech, (on Briarcliff Lodge stationery), undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Notes for speech, undated (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Notes for speech, (on Senate stationary, re: colonial history), undated (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Notes for speech, (economic history of US), undated (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Notes for speech, (economics), undated (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Notes for speech, (Philippines), undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Notes for speech, (some on RMS Baltic stationary), undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Notes for speech, (statistics), undated (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Notes for speech, (summary of NY Central RR operations), undated (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Notes for speech, (list of treaties), undated (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Reference material, The Calendar, Civil and Ecclesiastical, Mercersberg Review, 1858 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Reference material, Christian Union and Liturgical Tendencies of the Times, 1859 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Reference material, Brief, On Appeal of Benner and LaFollette, 1897 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Reference material, Statement of Facts and Law, Great Falls VA, 1898 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Reference material, La Langue Bleue, 1899 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Reference material, Albert J. Beveridge speech, Congressional Record, 1908 (Box 16, Folder 49)
- Scrapbooks, 1872-1921; MS2095 Series 3; 9 Linear feet (Box 34, Box 32, Box 33, Box 30, Box 31, Box 29, Box 28, Box 27, Box 26, Box 25, Box 24, Box 23, Box 22, Box 21, Box 20, Box 19, Box 18, Box 17)
  This series consists of thirty-four scrapbooks kept from 1872-1921, each identified on the exterior by dates and descriptions. Some are in poor condition. The scrapbooks contain clippings of speech transcripts and articles relating to current events and to Depew's public activities and oratory, including some unfavorable reviews. Some scrapbooks also contain clippings of notices relating to Depew's personal life, and some appear to be about topics of interest to him personally.
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 17)
  - Scrapbook, "Campaign speeches and literature. None of them by Depew. He probably used them as sources of material for his own speeches. Campaigns of 1872-1876." Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 18)
  - Scrapbook, "2 1870-1889," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 1876-1889 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, "7 Misc. 1876-1890," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 1881-1891 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 19)
  - Scrapbook, "8 Mostly 1890 - Some 1887-89 Private Book," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 1884-1891 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, "1 New Items 1885-1886-1887," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 1885-1887 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 20)
  - Scrapbook, "5 Largely 1890 May-June, Some 1887-1889," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 1886-1890 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, "4 Campaign Book 1888," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 21)
  - Scrapbook, "6 Nov 1888-1890 Political," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, "9," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 07/-, 09/1890 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 22)
  - Scrapbook, "10 Depew speeches & Interviews 1891 May-June," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 05/1891-06/1891 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, "11," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 1891-1892 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 23)
  - Scrapbook, "12 1892 Jan -June," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, "13 Depew speeches, etc, October 1892," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 10/1892 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 24)
  - Scrapbook, "14 January to April, 1893," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 04/1893 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 25)
  - Scrapbook, "15," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 03/1894-06/1894 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, "16 July 5th to Sept 17th, 1894," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 07/1894-09/1894 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 26)
  - Scrapbook, "18 Apr - June, 1895 Largely political," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 04/1895-06/1895 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, "17 Personal clippings Sept 8 - Nov 30, 1895," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 09/1895-11/1895 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 27)
  - Scrapbook, "19 Dec 1st 1895 - Feb 29, 1896," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 12/1895-02/1896 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, "20 June 1st to Sept 31st, 1896," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 06/1896-09/1896 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 28)
  - Scrapbook, "21 June 1st-Dec 31st, 1897," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 06/1897-12/1897 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 29)
  - Scrapbook, "22 General campaign material 1900," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 30)
  - Scrapbook, "23" Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 1900 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, "July - Sept 1900," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 07/1900-09/1900 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 31)
  - Scrapbook, "24 Campaign Book of 1900 including Depew speeches," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 09/1900 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, "1900 Campaign Book," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 10/1900 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 32)
  - Scrapbook, "28," Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 1901-1902 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, "27 Gen news largely political. 1902.Very little on Depew." Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, "29 Gen News - chiefly political. Largely 1907.Some 1906.Not on Depew." Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 1906-1907 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 33)
  - Scrapbook, Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 1917 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 1917-1918 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 1919 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 1919-1920 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbooks, undated (Box 34)
  - Scrapbook, Clippings relating to speeches, campaigns, current events and personal life, 1920-1921 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Memorial books, 1928; MS2095 Series 4; 3 Linear feet (Box 38, Box 39, Box 40, Box 35, Box 37, Box 36)
  This series consists of six large volumes of clippings of news articles, editorials, obituaries and eulogies about Chauncey M. Depew. Also included are articles relating to his funeral and estate. The volumes all date from 1928.
  - Memorial books, undated (Box 35)
  - In Memoriam-Chauncey M. Depew-Volume I - - News clippings, obituaries, editorials etc. concerning death, funeral and estate of CMD., 04/05/1928-04/08/1928 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Memorial books, undated (Box 36)
  - In Memoriam-Chauncey M. Depew-Volume II - - News clippings, obituaries, editorials etc. concerning death, funeral and estate of CMD., 04/05/1928-04/08/1928 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Memorial books, undated (Box 37)
  - In Memoriam-Chauncey M. Depew-Volume III - - News clippings, obituaries, editorials etc. concerning death, funeral and estate of CMD., 04/05/1928-04/08/1928 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Memorial books, undated (Box 38)
  - In Memoriam-Chauncey M. Depew-Volume IV - - News clippings, obituaries, editorials etc. concerning death, funeral and estate of CMD., 04/05/1928-04/08/1928 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Memorial books, undated (Box 39)
  - In Memoriam-Chauncey M. Depew-Volume V - News clippings, obituaries, editorials etc. concerning death, funeral and estate of CMD., 04/05/1928-04/08/1928 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Memorial books, undated (Box 40)
  - In Memoriam-Chauncey M. Depew-Volume VI - News clippings, obituaries, editorials etc. concerning death, funeral and estate of CMD., 04/05/1928-04/08/1928 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Newspapers and clippings, 1854-1930; MS2095 Series 5; 1 Linear feet (Box 41, Box 45)
  This series includes newspapers and clippings relating to Chauncey Depew's public speaking career and to his widow's bequest to The George Washington University after his death.
  Speech transcripts dating from 1893-96, both of Depew's speeches and speeches made by others, are arranged chronologically. Clippings related to May Palmer Depew's bequest date from 1929-30 and are arranged alphabetically by the state of the publication's location.
  The series also contains some original newspapers in an oversized box, including one copy of The Yale Banner from 1854, when Depew was a student, and some special editions covering events involving Depew.
  - Newspapers and clippings, undated (Box 41)
  - Clipping, "The Farmers and the Crisis," The Sun, 09/10/1893 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Clipping, "McKinley Opens the Fight," New York Tribune, 09/13/1893 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Clipping, "The Note Sounded," Brooklyn (NY) Daily Eagle, 10/24/1893 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Clipping, "The President on Hawaii," New York Daily Tribune, 12/19/1893 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Clipping, "In Praise of the Pilgrims," New York Tribune, 12/23/1893 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Clipping, "American Elections," The Echo, London, 11/13/1894 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Clipping, "Abraham Lincoln's Birthday," Chattanooga (TN) Times, 02/13/1896 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Clipping, "Man of the People," Chicago Herald, (CMD Eulogy of Lincoln at the New York Republican Club's Banquet), 02/13/1896 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Clipping, "Foraker Speaks," Columbus (OH) Journal, 02/13/1896 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Clipping, "Commemorated Lincoln's Day," New York Mail and Express, 02/13/1896 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Clipping, "Imperishable Principles," San Francisco Call, 02/14/1896 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Clipping, "Two Political Perorations," New York Mail and Express, 02/24/1896 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Clipping, "Sketch of William McKinley," Syracuse (NY) Express, 03/05/1896 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Clipping, "Cullom Wroth," Boston Globe, 03/08/1896 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Clipping, "New's Name is Used," The Inter-Ocean, Chicago, 03/09/1896 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Clipping, "Sutherland in Indiana," Rochester (NY) Express, 03/10/1896 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Clipping, "McKinley is Leading," New York Herald, 03/16/1896 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Clipping, "West Side Men Rejoice," New York Daily News, 1896 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Clips, 1896 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Clipping, "Governor McKinley's Speech," unidentified newspaper, 1896 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Clipping, "Senator Thurston's Declaration," unidentified newspaper, Feb 19, 18, 1896 ca. (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Clipping, "Depew at His Best," Springfield (MA) Union, 11/19, _ (after 1901), undated (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Clipping, "Chauncey M. Depew and the Middle Class Union," unidentified newspaper, 1920 ca. (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Various Clippings, primarily relating to Mrs. Depew's bequest to GWU, Alabama, 1929 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Various Clippings, primarily relating to Mrs. Depew's bequest to GWU, Arizona, 1929 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Various Clippings, primarily relating to Mrs. Depew's bequest to GWU, Arkansas, 1929 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Various Clippings, primarily relating to Mrs. Depew's bequest to GWU, California, 1929 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Various Clippings, primarily relating to Mrs. Depew's bequest to GWU, Colorado, 1929-1930 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Various Clippings, primarily relating to Mrs. Depew's bequest to GWU, Connecticut, 1929 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Various Clippings, primarily relating to Mrs. Depew's bequest to GWU, Delaware, 1929-1930 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Various Clippings, primarily relating to Mrs. Depew's bequest to GWU, Florida, 1929-1930 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Various Clippings, primarily relating to Mrs. Depew's bequest to GWU, Georgia, 1929-1930 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Various Clippings, primarily relating to Mrs. Depew's bequest to GWU, Idaho, 1929 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Various Clippings, primarily relating to Mrs. Depew's bequest to GWU, Illinois, 1929-1930 (Box 41, Folder 34)